<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trippin</string>
    <string name="varanasi">
        Varanasi, traditionally known as Banaras (Benares) in India, is a popular holy city of the nation located in the central region of the Ganges Valley in North India. This city is not just the oldest in India but happens to be the oldest colonized cities universally. Banaras has religious as well as literal significance. This city is known for world renowned universities like Banaras Hindu University (founded by Madan Mohan Malvia), Sampurnanand Sanskrit University and the Mahatma Gandhi Kashi Vidyapeeth. Therefore the city is generally referred to as the city of temples or the city of learning.

        <br><br>\n\n\nFamous things about varanasi:\n\n\n</br></br>
<br></br>
        <br>\n1.To start with, Varanasi is renowned for its paan.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n2.We also suggest you to taste some great chats at the Kashi Chat Center near the Godwila Crossing.\n\</br>
<br></br>
<br>\n3.Zaika (located in Shivala) is a popular Indian and Chinese restaurant.\n</br>
<br></br>
        <br>\n4.Varanasi is an interesting place where you can shop for multiple items like clothes, accessories, statues, handicrafts and mangoes.\n</br>
<br></br>
<br>\n5.The best places to shop for these handicrafts and sarees are the Thateri bazaar, the Temple bazaar, the Gyan Vapi and the Vishwanath Gali. If you wish to buy carpets, paintings and brassware, then Thateri bazaar is the right hunt for you.\n</br>

        <br><br>\n\n\nFamous Activities In varanasi:\n\n\n</br></br>
<br></br>
 <br>\n1.Witness Grandeur Evening Aarti Ceremony\n</br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n2.Morning Boat Ride in Ganges River\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n3.Explore Varanasi Temples\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n4.Go for a Sightseeing Tour of Sarnath\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n5.Take a Holy Bath in Ganges\n</br>
    </string>
    <string name="kerela">
       Kochi is in the state of Kerela. Called Gods Own Country by the tourist promoters of the state, if you visit you will find it difficult to refute this claim. Amongst the greenest states in India, it features coffee plantations and wild life sanctuaries. It is also home to the famous \'Backwaters\' and their houseboats. Activities such as day trips on the backwaters, such as coracle rowing, and swimming are popular here. Some five-star resorts even offer water sports of a more complex nature.Tradition and festivals are also a big draw for the state. Best time to visit is between November and March as the monsoons and summertime are best avoided.

<br><br>\n\n\nFamous things about Kerela:\n\n\n</br></br>
<br></br>
 <br>\n1.Indian Coffee House is a great place to taste south Indian food followed by some authentic filter coffee.\n</br>
          <br></br>
        <br>\n2.It has many antiques to offer as well. There are beautifully carved boxes, temples, miniature snake boats on offer as well.\n</br>
         <br></br>
        <br>\n3.The typical Kerala home is adorned with a lot of bronze artifacts. These will include the statues of animals, birds, Gods and Goddesses, Diya stands, Agarbatti stands and a whole lot more.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n4.The Keralite women are very fond of gold and jewelry. Unlike the semi precious stones from Rajasthan which are popular in the northern parts of India, here the yellow metal is favored.\n</br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n5.Kerala silk is very famous. The traditional bridal sari is made from raw material and has a border which is made of gold thread.</br>

<br><br>\n\n\nFamous Activities in Kerela:\n\n\n</br></br>
<br></br>
        <br>\n1.Cochin Golf Club is located on an island in the middle of Kochi and can only be approached by boat, which makes an interesting experience for any golf aficionado.\n</br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n2.It is possible to do some scuba diving in Kerala and enjoy the rich variety of underwater life. Kochi and Thiruvanthapuram both offer opportunities for scuba diving.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n3.Kerela has a couple of amusement parks on its outskirts. They usually have separate water and dry rides.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n4.Watching the colorful Snake Boat races in Alleppey is one of the most amazing things to do in Alleppey, Kerala.\n</br>
        <br>\n5.For one of the most fascinating activities to do in Kerala and its forests, Thekkady should be on the topmost list of places you are visiting in Kerala.\n</br>
    </string>
    <string name="goa">
        While the capital of Goa is Panjim, the action is not in the city centre but on the beaches all along the coast of the Arabian Sea. Local \'Shacks\' are seasonal structures that pop up on the beaches with the arrival of the first batch of tourists each year. Most of them are closed during the monsoon as the area gets decidedly waterlogged in rainy season. However in season the Shacks are strong competition to the permanent restaurants and eateries in the vicinity of the beaches.

To enjoy the beaches maybe it\'s best to take a long walk in the early morning sun. Most beaches melt into one another and it is possible to start walking at Fort Aguada and cross Candolim, Calangute and reach Baga before hitting a natural wall of rock that will end your progress.

<br><br>\n\n\nFamous things about Goa:\n\n\n</br></br>
<br><br></br></br>
        <br>\n1.The Wednesday market at Anjuna is a great place to shop for jewelry, leather goods, clothing, sunglasses, sarongs, bags, handicrafts, secondhand goods, books, and a whole lot more.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n2.If you miss the Wednesday flea market at Anjuna, don’t worry you can catch the night edition at Ingo’s and Mackies. Their Saturday Night Bazaar is essentially a replay of the Anjuna flea market.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n3.Bhagwan Mahavir Wildlife Sanctuary is most spectacular wild life sanctuary.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n4.There are many churches in Goa – a legacy of its colonial past. You must visit a few of them.\n</br>
        <br></br>
       <br>\n5.The Dudhsagar Falls are the most imposing in Goa and the second highest in India.\n</br>


<br><br>\n\n\nFamous Activities In Goa:\n\n\n</br></br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n1.There are motor boats available for hire at the beach that will offer to take you dolphin spotting for an hour.\n</br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n2.There are two and four-stroke engine Go Karts available here. It is the latest craze to hit Goa and locals and foreigners alike race to their heart’s content.\n</br>
        <br></br>
        <br>\n3.The GTDC (Goa Tourism Development Corporation) offers an hour-long cruise on the Mandovi River on the Santa Monica. \n</br>
        <br>\n4.This is the main pastime for majority of the tourist who head for the beaches of Goa. There are beachcombers, sunbathers, volleyball players and all sorts here\n</br>
        <br></br>
<br>\n5.Once you have done the mandatory sightseeing and peered through the telescopes, you can head down to the water. There are water scooters, boat rides, water-skiing and sailing on offer here.\n</br>
    </string>
</resources>